this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
i can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and
intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line to the new world
separated from the rest of his crew luffy is rushing to navy hq to rescue his brother ace from execution
meanwhile on marine ford home of navy hq the epic war over ace's life between the navy and the
white beard pirates has begun yasakani sacred jewel
hmm my fault i really should have known better if your boss was that easy to kill you wouldn't be here
right now would you
what the hell is he doing
try bucking this one
if we all left our posts
there'd be no one here to do their job
sure like to be flashy don't they
think i'll have you light the candles for my next birthday you magma punk
i'd rather provide the lighting for your funeral how about it old man
the descendant of the beast little oris jr full speed ahead
how utterly repulsive men are bothersome enough at normal size
such a magnificent beast
if i can just get my hands on his dead body i'll have another giant zombie that hopefully lasts longer
than the first one
make your way to the scaffold watch your backs
the giant units moving out
swallow your fear
they're trying to head off oris jr
time to live up to our duty he can't defeat us all
that thing is impossibly huge he's at least twice as big as a common giant keep shooting he's a living
creature
i can't say we were expecting such a powerful beast
you're an easy target for them please turn around
i'm coming for you
oh holy crap kill that beast
oh it's opened up a path for us to get into the bay
and then the plaza
damn it all fall back tighten up the defensive line and don't let them get to the plaza
how
so
I want to run, but I don't know where to go!
Stand down or die, Navy!
Nobody needs you getting in the way.
Rear Admiral Yukimura, slayer of a thousand men.
I swear.
What the hell are you doing?
We're at war here.
We don't have any use for the weak.
I'm useless.
I'm totally pathetic.
I've never had to crane my head up to look at anyone.
Me neither.
Out of the way!
Ace is my friend and he needs my help.
Don't try to stop me!
I'll take my orders from you!
Roar!
Vice Admiral LaCroix!
That oars is just as stubborn as he ever was.
Getting yourself killed does not make you brave.
Don't stop me, Pops.
I won't stop, because I don't want to.
Not till I'm done, not till he's the same.
I want to save my bro.
I want to do it now so it doesn't hurt no more.
I know the feeling.
All right, men! Help out the big guy!
Go cover oars!
Yeah!
Howie was supposed to find that thing?
He's too big!
Don't worry, Vice Admiral. I'll avenge you!
We can't do this alone. We're all gonna have to attack at once.
Horse is one hell of a destruction. Let's make our move!
Slave arrow!
Wait, what? They're statues!
South!
Oh!
You're the pirate empress, huh?
Yeah!
Oh!
Wait, what?
They're statues!
So!
You're the pirate empress, huh?
Yeah!
What did you do to me?
I'm crumbling!
Perfume!
Hazel!
Agh!
Death!
Oh!
Ugh!
Huh?
Oh!
What did you do to me?
I'm crumbling!
Perfume!
Viva!
Agh!
Woah!
Whoa!
Agh!
You psycho!
Why are you attacking the Marines?
I may have agreed to aid you in your fight against Whitebeard's crew,
but I don't recall making any promises about collateral damage.
Allies or foes, all men are equally worthless.
Well, except for one.
You can hate me if you want, but you can't say that I didn't keep my word.
You're nuts!
Won't you at least take mercy on my beauty?
Uh, why not?
I'm coming, Ace!
Yes, right this way.
Now, Oz!
You're done!
I'm done!
To be continued...
I'm gonna save you now, Ace!
Stop!
I'm gonna save you now!
Prepare yourself for the Ursa Shock!
Oars!
That's enough!
They won't let you reach me!
I'm gonna save you now!
Hey, buddy!
It's hard to tell from all the way down here, but I can't help but wonder.
Don't you get hot?
Just being closer to the sun and all.
I am hot!
I'm gonna save you now!
What are you doing outside in the rain?
Rain or shine, I am doing fine!
I don't get wet anymore!
Wow, I love this hat!
I still can't reach you.
If I can't save you, at least I can take out one of the warlords!
Hahaha!
Why'd you stop? Ace is right there!
Ow, my foot!
Captain!
Hey, Captain! You're gonna stay outside again?
Why should I care? The snow's not getting on my head!
In the heat of the gold, this hat never gets old!
You're the best, Ace!
Now that was fun!
Oz!
Wait, he's still moving?
He's infiltrated the plaza!
Gotta go a little bit more!
Don't worry, Ace! I can make it for sure!
That damn Doflamingo! He knew I wanted oars intact!
You don't cut the foot off a corpse someone's claimed!
Doppelman!
Finish him!
Spocky Shadow Lizard!
No!
Ha!
Oh!
He's inside the plaza!
You're so happy!
No!
That damn Doflamingo!
He knew I wanted oars intact!
You don't cut the foot off a corpse someone's claimed!
I made it, Ace. I'm here to save you.
After Orz Jr. risks his life to pave the way forward, the Whitebeard Pirates rush for the execution platform.
However, just as their rescue mission begins to pick up momentum, Sengoku employs a surprise tactic that turns the tide yet again.
On the next, One Piece! Justice for the winners! Sengoku's strategy in action! I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!